♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Good evening, Quahog.
I'm Tom Tucker.
Our top story tonight:
In a shocking turn of events,
the city of Detroit
has officially given up.
The now former mayor has given
the key to the city
back to the Huron Indian tribe.
So, farewell, Detroit.
From Bob Seger to Axel Foley,
we never really cared. Joyce?
Thanks, Tom.
In local news,
Quahog is expecting
a special guest this weekend,
famed Asian
competitive eating champion
Charles Yamamoto.
Yamamoto has not yet lost
a hot dog eating competition
on his world tour.
But if you think
you have what it takes
to beat the best eater
in the world,
come down to the James Woods
High parking lot this Saturday
with $50 and a large appetite.
Wow, maybe you should
enter the contest, Dad.
I'll bet
you could win.
Well, I would, Chris,
if I wasn't so
obsessed with my figure.
Wait a minute.
Chris, have you ever
eaten anything?
Only, like, all the time!
Perfect! Now we just
need the 50 bucks.
Damn it, I knew I shouldn't
have named that star for Mort.
Ugh! Just give me the money.
Peter, we're not
spending $50
so Chris can stuff his
face with hot dogs.
All right, fine.
I'll figure out a way
to get the cash myself.
I'm a smart guy.
Peter, no, you're not.
Don't you feel ridiculous now?
All right, Chris,
if we're gonna pay the entry fee
for that eating contest,
we got to sell some
of my old stuff.
What are these, Dad?
Oh, wow.
I haven't seen
those in a while.
Those are my old Playboys
from the '70s.
Oh, my God, this one's so hot.
You can almost see
a little bit of woman.
Wow, Peter, you've got some
pretty cool albums here.
Yeah, well, I was one
cool potato back in the day.
You know, some of these might
actually be worth something.
Look at this--
Beatles, Rolling Stones.
Oh, my God, I haven't seen
this one in forever.
Look-Look at this. Queen,
News of the World.
Check it out.
Aah!
Oh, what's the matter?
What the hell is that?!
A killer robot monster?!
No, it's News of the World.
It's an album
by the band Queen. See?
Aah!
Stewie, relax.
No, Brian! You keep
that thing away from me!
Is it... Is it looking at me?!
Can it see me?!
(laughing): Man, you're really scared
of this thing, huh?
Does it eat little boys?!
I don't know. Maybe,
if it's hungry.
(yelling)
Here's 50 bucks.
I'm taking this album.
Oh, wow, check
it out, Chris!
We got our entry fee
for the eating contest!
Now for the
next five days,
we're gonna focus on
nothing but training.
We'll even get up at
the crack of dawn.
(snoring)
(whispering):
Dad?
Dad, it's time to get up.
Oh, jeez, Chris,
it's the crack of dawn.
Yeah, but Dad, you
said to wake you up.
Yeah... Yeah, but, uh...
(mumbling)
Just... get-get...
get in...
get in the bed
with me and your mom.
Okay, but what
about training?
Oh, you smell
like melted cheese.
Yummy, yummy, yummy,
yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy.
(yawns) Good morning, Rupert.
Please tell me you set the timer
on the coffeemaker
because I completely forgot.
(yelling)
(laughing)
You son of a bitch!
Good morning.
Thought I'd help you wake up.
God, why does he look sad?!
He's already
destroyed mankind!
What else could he want?!
Hey, Carl.
Hey, can I get a couple
of scratch-off lottery tickets?
Oh, sure, Brian.
Ooh, Brian, can I do one?
I love scratchers!
Well, all right,
maybe just one.
Cherry.
Another cherry.
Oh, come on, one more, one more!
(yelling)
Thanks, Carl.
Yeah, you're welcome.
That was fun.
See you later.
Hey, uh, thanks
for letting me be Yoda.
Yup.
What is this?
("Pop Goes the Weasel" plays)
(music stops)
(music resumes)
(boing)
Oh-ho-ho,
what was I worried about?
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Oh, God!
Aah! Aah!
He's bleeding, man!
He's bleeding, and nobody's
doing anything about it!
I'll tell you what the news
of the world is.
We're in a lot
of (bleep) trouble!
(cheering and applause)
All right, Chris,
this is it.
This is what we've
been working for.
If you get nervous, just
picture the audience naked
and slide those hot
dogs down your throat.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome
to the World Hot Dog Eating
Championship Competition!
Please welcome our undefeated
champion eater,
Charles Yamamoto!
(cheering and applause)
Oh, my God, that guy is huge.
All right, eaters,
you have ten minutes.
On your marks,
get set, eat!
(cheering and whistling)
Come on, Chris.
You're doing great.
Just keep going.
You're almost there.
Well, I'd better get a move on.
Time's almost up!
It's gonna be a close one!
Chris, you're four
hot dogs behind!
Come on! Hurry!
Oh! I can't eat anymore.
Remember what I told you.
I get these weird cyst things
right on the fringe of my sac.
I want to get 'em checked,
but I'm afraid
of what they're gonna tell me.
He's right. I can do it!
(buzzer sounds, cheering)
ANNOUNCER:
We have a winner!
Ladies and gentlemen, Yamamoto
has finally been defeated!
(cheering, applause
and whistling)
Chris, you did it.
You're a champion!
And now you get your
pick of the groupies.
They're shiny.
Yeah, it's a
pretty warm day.
Oh!
Hey, hey, hey,
there, champ!
Aw, look at
him, Lois.
Relaxing after
his big victory.
Peter, he's not relaxing.
He's in a great deal of pain.
Damn it, don't you
see what you did to him?
I told you not to take him
to that eating competition,
and you deliberately defied me!
All right, what's
this really about?
Peter, Chris is
already overweight.
We need to start taking
responsibility for his health.
So I decided to sign him up
for fat camp.
What?! Mom, I don't want
to go to fat camp!
I'm sorry, sweetie.
It's for your own good.
And trust me, you'll feel
much better about yourself.
Everyone's gonna
make fun of me!
Oh, come on, who's
gonna make fun of you?
Hey, fatty, I hear
you're going to fat camp.
That's where
you belong!
Peter, stop it!
And I'd better not see
you at the big dance!
Come on, you.
Sorry, Chris.
I-I'm gonna go with him.
Hi. Welcome to
Camp Fresh Start.
Yeah, our son's gross,
so here we are.
The name's
Griffin.
Ah, yes,
Chris Griffin.
We have you staying
in the Broccoli Cabin.
So you guys are just
gonna leave me here?
Yeah, honey.
That's what camp is.
I don't want to stay!
Please take me home!
I don't want to go to fat camp!
Aw, come on, Chris.
Your mother's right.
This'll be good for you.
Well, how come you
don't have to go?!
You're fatter
than I am!
Huh. Good question, Peter.
How come
you don't have to go?
What are you
talking about?
Well, you're the one
who entered him
in that hot dog
eating contest.
Besides, he's right.
You could stand to lose
a few pounds yourself.
Unless you don't think
you could handle it.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I think I can.
What was that?
Never you mind
what that was.
(birds singing)
(trash can lid clanging)
Rise and shine, everyone!
What do you got there?
A candy bar, huh?
Got any other
contraband?
No.
Don't lie to me.
My father was a lawyer.
Oh, so your dad
gets guys off.
(laughing)
Peter Griffin.
Cabin clown.
Where's your bag, fatty?
You're welcome to
search my "beef case."
But there's
"mutton" in there.
(laughs) Peter Griffin.
Cabin clown.
You're in big trouble, mister.
Oh, there's no pulling the
wool over this guy's eyes.
Looks like I'd better
go on the "lamb."
Peter Griffin.
Cabin clown.
I think I'm gonna do okay here
at fat camp.
You sure you got
the "chops" for it?
Knock it off.
I'm the cabin clown.
(owl hooting)
And then he went
into the kitchen,
slowly opened the refrigerator,
and it was empty!
(all gasp)
So then, the man,
weak with hunger,
raced from the refrigerator
to the counter
to look for a delivery menu,
but all he could find was one
for a vegan place!
(all yell)
Vegan places aren't
real, right?
No, they're not real.
Or are they?!
Aah! Salad!
(all yelling)
Thank you
for sharing, Leonard.
And I think getting a new couch
was the way to go.
Is there someone else
who has a story
they'd like to share? Peter?
Uh, yeah, sure.
This one time,
I was on a city bus,
and the guy next to me
was eating a bucket
of fried chicken.
- Mmm! - Ooh!
Yum!
And the smell was
getting to me, you know.
And even though
I didn't know the guy,
I just dug in
and started stuffing
that chicken into my mouth.
O-Oh!
Embarrassing.
I've done that.
It was so delicious.
But... it wasn't
fried chicken.
It was a baby!
(crying):
It was a baby.
(sobbing)
Stewie?
Rupert, we won't give
that evil robot
the satisfaction of killing us.
We'll go together
on our own terms.
See you on the other side.
(gunshot)
Oh, my God!
Stewie, no!
What the hell's
wrong with you?!
It's that robot!
He killed Queen,
and now he's going to kill me!
He didn't kill Queen.
They're all fine.
Most of them are fine.
Look, Stewie, I'm sorry
for scaring you, all right?
But come on,
it's not a real robot.
See? It, It's
just an album. Look.
Here, you want
to hit it?
Well... I'm usually more
comfortable around things
if I can put them
in my mouth.
So, can I put it
in my mouth?
I guess.
This is just an album!
Yeah, that's what I've
been trying to tell you.
So, you know,
can you forgive me?
Oh, I suppose so.
I mean, Magellan forgave
the "Land Ho" prankster.
Land ho!
Where?! Where?!
Psych! Made you
look, loser.
Good thing
there wasn't land
or else you'd have
to meet the natives
with that mustard stain on your shirt.
What stain?
Ah! (blows raspberry)
Ugh! Why did I even bring
you on this trip?!
Because I'm the best
damn land spotter
in all of Europe.
It's true.
You are the best.
Yeah, I don't need you
to tell me that.
(birds chirping)
(both panting)
Dad, I can't take
this anymore.
I'm so tired
and I'm so hungry.
I got an idea, Chris.
Follow me.
What are we doing?
I saw a forest like this
in a book one time,
and I know there's a gingerbread
house out here somewhere.
Do you think
we could find it?!
We have to, Chris.
We-we gotta eat something
besides what
they're feeding us.
I know what
you mean, Dad.
I'm so hungry I could
eat this dead camper.
Holy crap!
(flies buzzing)
Well, we clearly don't have
all the evidence yet,
but that's never
stopped us before, right?
(laughs)
Oh, there's no other cops here.
But we do know one thing,
this kid was murdered.
(all gasp)
Murdered?!
Who in the world
would want to
kill a camper?
Don't look at me.
I'm just here to
drop off my son.
Justin? Justin,
that does not work for me.
And it looks like there
are signs of trauma
around the throat.
Somebody strangled
this fat kid.
Wait. He was strangled?
Yeah.
Joe, I know
who did it.
You do? Who?
Well, there's
only one person I know
who likes to strangle fat guys:
Patrick Pewterschmidt.
Who's that?
My brother-in-law.
People call him
"The Fat Guy Strangler."
He's always had a thing
for strangling fat guys.
I guess he fits
the profile, Peter,
but Lois's brother is
locked up in an asylum.
Well, either way,
we gotta get out of here.
Otherwise,
we're just sitting ducks!
Hey, we all know this guy
goes for the classy ladies.
In fact, I once
caught him trying
to pick up
a quack whore.
(all laugh)
All right, calm down.
We all make bad choices.
(phone rings)
Hello?
Lois, I hope
you're sitting down.
I got something
to tell ya.
Oh, God, what's wrong?
Is everything okay?
Is it Chris?
No, it's Peter,
your husband.
But I'm calling
with big news.
I was Anita in
the camp production
of West Side Story.
Peter, you know you're terrible
at patter songs.
I did okay.
♪ (mumbles lyrics) ...America ♪
♪ (mumbles) ...America ♪
♪ (mumbling) ...America ♪
♪ (mumbling) ...America. ♪
I got other news, too.
One of the fat kids at camp
got strangled!
(gasps) Oh, my God!
Yeah, but don't worry.
It ain't your brother.
He's still locked up
in that asylum.
Um, Mom...
look who dropped
by for a visit.
Hello, Lois.
(gasps) Patrick!
It's been
a long time.
(hushed):
Peter, he's here!
Wait a second, Lois,
I want to go back
to what you said
about my patter singing.
Who gives you
the right?!
You know I carried
Pirates of Penzance
that season at Quahog
Community Theater.
♪ I am the
(sings gibberish) ...general ♪
♪ (sings gibberish) ...mineral ♪
♪ (sings gibberish)
...historical ♪
...with the eggs on top. ♪
Man, I hope we get back
to your house
before Patrick hurts
anyone else!
If he even lays
a finger on my family,
I'll do to him
what I did to the Riddler.
(tires squeal)
Freeze, psycho!
Oh, Peter, thank God!
Patrick Pewterschmidt,
you're under arrest
for the murder of, uh...
(bleep)
I didn't get
the kid's name.
We're supposed to do that.
Lois, you called
the cops?
Patrick, you're my brother and
I love you, but you're not well.
But I'm better now.
I've put my past
behind me.
Save it, Patrick.
We know you escaped
from the asylum and killed...
Bill, we'll just call him
"Bill" for now.
Escaped?
I-I didn't escape.
Just this morning, a very nice
gentleman opened my cell door
and said I was
free to go.
Yeah, nice try.
That's not how it works.
Uncle Patrick, why do you
strangle fat people?
It's probably
a weird fetish thing.
Some criminals have 'em.
Like those anal-retentive
bandits
who robbed Quahog Bank
last year.
All right, hands in the air!
Vertically!
Both arms should be
parallel to each other!
You, fill this bag with clean,
unmarked bills!
But first fix that notepad
so it's at a right angle
with the corner of your desk!
And tap that pile of receipts
against a flat surface
so they're not sticking out
haphazardly!
You know what?!
Forget about the money!
Everybody grab a broom!
We are straightening
this place up!
All right, campers,
until the Fat Guy Strangler
is caught,
everyone has to stay
inside their cabins.
Now I'm gonna do
a stomach count.
When I call your name,
please respond.
Jenkins?
(stomach growls)
Robertson?
Davis?
(stomach growls)
Elliot?
Where's Elliot?
I think he's asleep.
Elliot?
Elliot, wake up.
Elliot? (gasps)
(phone rings)
Officer Swanson here.
What?! Oh, my God!
What is it, Joe?
Another camper was strangled
half an hour ago.
But... that means...
Patrick can't be
the killer.
That's what I was
trying to tell you.
Acknowledged. I'm on it.
Joe, would you settle
a camp argument?
Is it "Bombardment"
or "Dodgeball"?
Dodgeball.
Ah, you don't know.
Well, I'd better
put out an APB
to all
the neighboring towns.
Oh, the murderer won't leave
the camp.
What?
What are you talking about?
He's "feeding."
He killed twice and
he's gonna do it again.
He's got plenty of places
to hide out there
and a fully stocked corral
of victims.
How do you know that?
Trust me. I know.
You know, Joe, maybe Patrick can
actually be of help.
I mean, who better to get
inside the mind of someone
who's strangling fat people
than someone who's done it himself?
Yeah, give him a chance, Joe.
Like I did with scary teenagers.
I used to be afraid of 'em,
until I realized
they were just misunderstood.
Hey, fat ass,
give me your wallet!
I could give you
my wallet,
but what I think
you really want...
is love.
(voice breaks):
It's true!
I'm taking your shoes.
Poor kid.
You know,
the weirdest thing is
his bunk is right next
to Chris's.
Yeah, that was
a close call.
Oh, it was more
than a close call.
You said the first victim was
wearing a baseball cap,
this second one is blond...
The killer wasn't trying
to murder this kid.
He was trying to murder Chris.
(gasps) Oh, my God!
W-Why would anyone
want to kill Chris?
I don't know,
but I do know
that he's in a great deal
of danger right now.
Come on. Let's go!
Yeah!
But wait, this is our last
chance to do a panty raid!
(women scream)
Yay! Fat camp!
We got it!
Oh, no, a gust of wind!
(rustling)
(creaking)
(gasps) Wha, what
are you doing here?
You dishonored me,
Chris Griffin.
No one has ever eaten
more hot dogs than me.
Now you must die!
(gagging)
(glass shattering)
(groans)
(gasps)
(gagging)
STEWIE: Hey, fat ass!
I got news for you.
The News of the World!
(screams)
Why does robot hold
dead people?!
Is that future or past?!
(gasping and groaning)
Oh, my God, Stewie,
you saved my life!
Ah, you would've done
the same for me, Chris.
The important thing is,
we're all gonna be okay.
Right, Giant Robot?
Charles Yamamoto...
went from eating champion
to cold-blooded killer.
Who'd have thought?
Wait a minute, Joe.
That's the guy who opened
the door to my cell
yesterday and told me
I could leave
the asylum.
Huh. Is that right?
Well, then it
all makes sense.
Yamamoto wanted it
to look like
you broke out
on your own.
That way,
when he murdered Chris,
it was a cinch that you would
take the blame.
Well, Patrick, I guess
we all owe you an apology.
Patrick?
Where did he go?
He was just
right here.
What happened?!
Damn it!
He must've gotten away!
How is that possible?!
I don't know,
but I'd better make it
look like there
was a struggle.
Someone punch me
in the face.
I'm a good friend
to you.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru